hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Life podcast my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and I want to talk about today is
dealing with that worry and fear that
comes in it's natural it's normal I deal
with it myself sometimes where I see
things that aren't going how I want them
to or I see something that didn't go my
way and I start to get worried or I see
something that I'm not sure if it's
going to happen how I want it to and I
start to become fearful I want to tell
you this the number one thing that we
have to do we have to take control of
our thoughts your thought life is one of
the number one things that determines
your ability to
succeed what you attract in your life
and the results that you get I found
myself that often times I let my
thoughts just run my life go to and fro
everywhere in all directions and then
wondered why I'm not getting the kind of
results that I want and unfortunately
it's because because what we put in
ultimately creates what comes out if all
you're doing is scrolling social media
all day long looking at the news or
you're you know playing video games or
watching Netflix or TV shows that's all
you're consuming as content you're not
feeding your mind you're not staying
focused and disciplined in your business
you're not and and by the way those are
all great things and that might even
come from a place of of fear and worry
that you're doing those things it can
but what I want to talk about is is that
if you are focused so much on the
negative of what could go wrong and your
reasons for wanting to avoid those
negative things they become a
self-fulfilling prophecy and so we got
to flip the script we need to focus in
on what are the positive things that I
want to happen what are those things
that I desire to happen and then we
start declaring them and we start
believing that we're coming into
alignment with those things in our life
that our life is going to go well for us
that good things are starting to happen
for us we start to think on the things
that are good we start to imagine using
our
imagination that things are going to go
well now you might say well Jeremiah I
don't want to be
disappointed and this is where we have
to learn to not attach our happiness our
safety our security in life to avoiding
disappointment to making sure that
things don't ever disappoint us I think
often times that that really is the root
there is that if something doesn't go my
way or I hoped for something really well
that it didn't happen how I wanted to
now I just feel so devastated instead of
learning to surrender it Let It Go not
become so attached to those things that
are happening you know I teach this
often times to my clients and if you're
listening to this right now you're
getting a very high level teaching I'm
about to share with you in marketing
when we're marketing our business we
leading with attachment outcome what are
the things that we're leading people to
the outcomes and the desires that they
have the sales copy that we're creating
our offers around is connected around
the things that people desire to happen
for them the the the outcomes that
people want to
create in your life and in your business
it's important to learn how to connect
the dots with those things and to
communicate them in a powerful powerful
way that's what a good business owner
does with their ability to be able to
Market write sales copy but when it
comes to in your life this is what you
need to learn about your happiness and
by the way this is about your actions
this is about your discipline it's about
your ability to do the things that you
need to do to stay
focused to make good decisions you want
to
really let go
of those desires that you have that need
that insatiable need for things to go
your way that can motivate you to make
changes that can motivate you to do
things in your life that can motivate
you to take actions but when we let them
run our life and that we get so caught
up and upset when things don't go our
way we get so caught up and upset when
things don't happen how we want them
to it can really really derail our
ability to see possibilities step into
things going our way and actually
creating the kind of life that we want
we have the ability to create the life
that we want you have the ability to
create any life experience that you want
you have the ability to take anything
you could imagine and turn it into
reality we all do but often times the
reason why we're not is because we
become so attached to that Vision that
we don't do anything because we want to
avoid disappointment and we get so upset
when things don't go our way and we're
focused on self- protection we're
protecting ourselves so
much from those things happening not
even bad things happening protecting
ourselves so much from just stuff not
going how I want it to
that it stops us from being able to be
successful it stops us from being able
to connect with the people that were
meant to connect with our energy that we
show up in the world with the energy
that we show up in conversations
communication connection when you're
trying to create webinars and content
your energy is off people can feel it
they don't want to connect with somebody
that's that's has that energy they don't
feel safe they don't
feel excited fun about it and that's the
energy that you want what's going to
attract the energy to you that you need
is more from a childlike place it's from
a place
of having fun with things it's from a
place of enjoyment it's from a place of
excitement it's from a place of
enthusiasm and when you can learn to
connect your desires what you want to
happen to of Faith and Hope and
believing and this isn't tied to any
kind of Faith or religion of any kind
but the faith and belief that things are
going to work out well for me because
they always do that things are going to
go well for me that things are always
going to work out in my favor that
everything in my life is going to come
together for me for good and we start to
believe that and we start to hope that
and we start to step into that as our
reality
we start to own that as our
personality and we start to transform
our life and everything around
us to start to
focus on what are those things what are
those good things what are those things
that I have hope for what are those
things that
are
wonderful what are those things that are
beautiful what of those things that I'm
imagining is going really really well
for me I want I want to challenge you in
this in the toughest moment of your
life in the toughest
situation that you just want to cry
crawl under the covers and give up I
want you to imagine that things are
actually working out really well for you
that things are going the best for you
that they ever could have and this isn't
about spiritual by passing or anything
about ignoring reality at all this is
about learning to visualize and to say
you know what what happened today is
temporary it doesn't have to be forever
and it can change because I have the
ability to change my life my existence
my
future for
good and that my friends is a beautiful
thing that my friends is a wonderful
thing and so we have to we have to we
have
to learn to control our thoughts learn
to control our
emotions away from the worst case
scenario the self- protection the trying
to make sure that everything is going
perfect I get it you might be listening
to this right now because that's what
you want you want things to go well for
you you want things to go perfectly for
you but can I tell you this what's
perfect for you often is not what you
imagine but it's something that's better
that God is going to bring into your
life that's greater than anything that
you could possibly
imagine and so instead of trying to
force your way of things surrendering it
to a higher power that knows better than
you and
believing that that's
much much better much Superior in all
ways and letting go of well I want this
for me I want this my way and control
control
control you know actually the best way
to actually get control of your life and
for things to go the way you really
truly want them to deep inside because
we all have desires what we truly want
the way to actually get what we truly
want is to learn to let go is to learn
to surrender is to learn to give up that
control to go with the
flow now I'm not say that you are
passive I'm not saying that you don't
ask for what you want I'm not saying
that you don't go and get what you want
I'm not saying that you don't go and
take what you
can those are all good things but I what
I am saying is that life is very
interesting things don't always pan out
the way that we imagined but it always
works out for good every single time and
so I hope that this encourages you here
today I can tell you as somebody who has
experienced a lot of crazy stuff in my
life that every time that I thought that
things were going terribly for me and I
got scared and worried and things
weren't going how I wanted them to it
always was a setup for something much
better much more beautiful much more
amazing in the end on the other side of
it and it could be that way for you as
well all right I'll talk to you soon
have a good one share this episode with
somebody who needs encouragement how I'm
do jeremi
[Music]
[Applause]